{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "6 \times 2",
            "isMcq": false,
            "answer": "12",
            "numberInputType": "mix,cfr"
        },
        {
            "question": "2 \times 2",
            "isMcq": null,
            "answer": "4",
            "numberInputType": "mix,cfr,dec"
        },
        {
            "question": "4 \times 10",
            "answer": "40",
            "numberInputType": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "12 \times 2",
            "answer": "24",
            "numberInputType": null
        },
        {
            "question": "11 \times 12",
            "answer": "132",
            "numberInputType": "int"
        },
        {
            "question": "8 \times 11",
            "answer": "88",
            "numberInputType": "int"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 \times 6",
            "answer": "60"
        },
        {
            "question": "2 \times 8",
            "answer": "16",
            "numberInputType": "dec,cfr"
        },
        {
            "question": "3 \times 12",
            "answer": "36",
            "numberInputType": "dec,mix"
        },
        {
            "question": "11 \times 2",
            "answer": "22",
            "numberInputType": "dec,int"
        }
    ]
}